Finding Aid for Detroit News records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Scrapbooks
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 10 I-K, 1945-1965 (Box 60)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 11 L-M, 1944-1981 (Box 61)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 12 M, 1950-1969 (Box 61)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 13 M-N, 1945-1977 (Box 61)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 14 N-O, 1952-1969 (Box 61)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 15 P, 1946-1964 (Box 62)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 16 P, 1948-1962 (Box 62)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 17 P, 1948-1956 (Box 62)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 18 P, 1952-1960 (Box 62)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 19 R-S, 1945-1964 (Box 63)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 20 S, 1948-1959 (Box 63)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 21 S, 1958-1971 (Box 63)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 22 T, 1953-1965 (Box 63)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 23 T-V, 1951-1967 (Box 64)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 24 W-Z and Miscellaneous, 1942-1978 (Box 64)
  - Eisenhower, Mrs. Dwight D., 1952-1979 (Box 64)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1976-1982 (Box 64)
  - Faubus, Orval E.-Politician, 1957-1962 (Box 64)
  - Ferency, Zolton A.-Politician, 1960-1986 (Box 65)
  - Ferguson, Homer-Politician-Book 1 A-M, 1940-1969 (Box 65)
  - Ferguson, Homer-Politician-Book 2 N-Z and Miscellaneous, 1924-1948 (Box 65)
  - Fitzgerald, Frank D.-Politician-Book 1 A-K, 1931-1939 (Box 65)
  - Fitzgerald, Frank D.-Politician-Book 2 L-Z and Miscellaneous, 1932-1939 (Box 65)
  - Football-Games-Goodfellow, 1942-1967 (Box 66)
  - Football-Games-Rose Bowl, 1932-1981 (Box 66)
  - Football-National League-Detroit Lions-Games-Book 1 A-M, 1965-1979 (Box 66)
  - Football-National League-Detroit Lions-Games-Book 2 S-T, 1957-1980 (Box 66)
  - Football-National League-Detroit Lions-Games-Book 3 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1958-1971 (Box 66)
  - Ford, Edsel, 1920-1980 (Box 67)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 1 A-B, 1953-1976 (Box 67)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 2 B-C, 1935-1976 (Box 67)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 3 C-F, 1956-1979 (Box 67)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 4 F-K, 1956-1976 (Box 68)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 5 L-N, 1958-1975 (Box 68)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 6 N, 1958-1976 (Box 68)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 7 O-P, 1974-1982 (Box 68)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 8 P, 1975-1976 (Box 69)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 9 P, 1944-1976 (Box 69)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 10 R-T, 1967-1977 (Box 69)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 11 T, 1973-1977 (Box 69)
  - Ford, Gerald-President-Book 12 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1959-1977 (Box 70)
  - Ford, Henry I-Auto Magnate-Book 1-A-D, 1927-1977 (Box 70)
  - Ford, Henry I-Auto Magnate-Book 2-B-G, 1923-1942 (Box 70)
  - Ford, Henry I-Auto Magnate-Book 3-G, 1929-1982 (Box 70)
  - Ford, Henry I-Auto Magnate-Book 4 G-M, 1926-1963 (Box 71)
  - Ford, Henry I-Auto Magnate-Book 5 M, 1928-1976 (Box 71)
  - Ford, Henry I-Auto Magnate-Book 7 S, 1919-1938 (Box 71)
  - Ford, Henry I-Auto Magnate-Book 8 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1928-1971 (Box 71)
  - Ford, Henry II-Auto Magnate-Book 1 A-B, 1952-1981 (Box 71)
  - Ford, Henry II-Auto Magnate-Book 2 C-F, 1966-1981 (Box 71)
  - Ford, Henry II-Auto Magnate-Book 3 F-P, 1953-1976 (Box 72)
  - Ford, Henry II-Auto Magnate-Book 4 R-T, 1967-1979 (Box 72)
  - Ford, Henry II-Auto Magnate-Book 5 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1953-1981 (Box 72)
  - Ford, Henry-Libel Suit Against Chicago Tribune-Libel Suit By Navy League-Miscellaneous, 1918-1919 (Box 72)
  - Ford, William Clay-Business Executive, 1938-1980 (Box 72)
  - Ford Motor Company-Employees-Collective Bargaining-UAW-Book 1-1937-1956 (Box 72)
  - Ford Motor Company-Employees-Collective Bargaining-UAW Book 2, 1956-1971 (Box 73)
  - Ford Motor Company-Employees-Collective Bargaining-UAW Book 3, 1972-1982 (Box 73)
  - Ford Motor Company-Employees-Strikes-Book 1, 1937-1949 (Box 73)
  - Ford Motor Company-Employees-Strikes-Book 2, 1949-1978 (Box 73)
  - Ford Motor Company-Stockholders Suit, 1927 (Box 73)
  - Franco, General Francisco-Spanish Diplomat, 1937-1975 (Box 73)
  - Franks, Roberts-Chicago -- Murdered, 1924 (Box 74)
  - Fulbright, J. William-Politician-Index, 1946-1976 (Box 74)
  - Gandhi, Mahatma-Indian Leader (Box 74)
  - Gangs-Detroit-Purple, 1928-1971 (Box 74)
  - Gas-Natural-Book 1-A-L, 1948-1979 (Box 74)
  - Gas-Natural-Book 2-M-Z and Miscellaneous, 1928-1979 (Box 74)
  - Gas-Natural-Book 3 Miscellaneous, 1937-1977 (Box 75)
  - Gas-Rates-Book 1 A, 1931-1982 (Box 75)
  - Gas-Rates-Book 2, 1977-1982 (Box 75)
  - Garland, Judy-Actress, 1939-1981 (Box 75)
  - General Motors Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining-Book 1 A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1936-1972 (Box 75)
  - General Motors Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining-Book 2 Miscellaneous, 1934-1969 (Box 75)
  - General Motors Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining-Book 3, 1970-1982 (Box 76)
  - General Motors Corporation-Employees-Strikes-Book 1 A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1937-1970 (Box 76)
  - General Motors Corporation-Employees-Strikes-Book 2 Miscellaneous, 1940-1966 (Box 76)
  - General Motors Corporation-Employees-Strikes-Book 3, 1967-1981 (Box 76)
  - Germany-Occupation-Book 1 A-B, 1946-1961 (Box 76)
  - Germany-Occupation-Book 2 B, 1951-1962 (Box 77)
  - Germany-Occupation-Book 3 B-N, 1945-1980 (Box 77)
  - Germany-Occupation-Book 4 O-R, 1945-1949 (Box 77)
  - Germany-Occupation-Book 5 R-Z and Miscellaneous, 1949-1981 (Box 77)
  - Gillespie, John-Politician, 1915-1948 (Box 77)
  - Girardin, Ray-Police Commission, 1960-1976 (Box 78)
  - Glenn, John-Astronaut, 1959-1982 (Box 78)
  - Goldberg, Arthur J.-Politician, 1960-1978 (Box 78)
  - Goldwater, Barry-Politician-Book 1 A-K, 1955-1982 (Box 78)
  - Goldwater, Barry-Politician-Book 2 L-P, 1954-1975 (Box 78)
  - Goldwater, Barry-Politician-Book 3 P, 1961-1964 (Box 79)
  - Goldwater, Barry-Politician-Book 4 R-Z and Miscellaneous, 1957-1982 (Box 79)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 1 A-B, 1921-1981 (Box 79)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 2 C-D, 1922-1981 (Box 79)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 3 E-K, 1931-1982 (Box 79)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 4 L-M, 1935-1982 (Box 80)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 5 M, 1921-1982 (Box 80)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 6 M, 1922-1976 (Box 80)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 7 N-O, 1921-1980 (Box 80)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 8 P-S, 1929-1981 (Box 80)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 9 S-W, 1923-1980 (Box 81)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 10 W, 1921-1975 (Box 81)
  - Golf-Championships-Book 11 W-Z and Miscellaneous, 1947-1981 (Box 81)
  - Golf-Championships-National (U.S.) Open, 1922-1982 (Box 81)
  - Golf-Championships-Professional Golfers' Association, 1925-1982 (Box 81)
  - Golf-Hole in One-Contests-Detroit News, 1928-1982 (Box 82)
  - Golf-Schools-Detroit News, 1936-1982 (Box 82)
  - Golf-Series-Book 1 A-J, 1950-1960 (Box 82)
  - Golf-Series-Book 2 J-Z and Miscellaneous, 1941-1969 (Box 82)
  - Governors-Conference-Book 1 A-Z and Miscellaneous 1923-1982 (Box 82)
  - Governors-Conference-Book 2 Miscellaneous, 1950-1975 (Box 82)
  - Graham, Billy-Evangelist, 1949-1974 (Box 83)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Duchess of Windsor, 1936-1974 (Box 83)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Duke of Windsor-Book 1, 1929-1940 (Box 83)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Duke of Windsor-Book 2, 1919-1966 (Box 83)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-King George VI, 1936-1957 (Box 83)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Princess Margaret-Book 1 A-T, 1930-1970 (Box 83)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Princess Margaret-Book 2 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1942-1971 (Box 84)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Queen Elizabeth II-Book 1 A-C, 1952-1979 (Box 84)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Queen Elizabeth II-Book 2 H-S, 1945-1972 (Box 84)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Queen Elizabeth II-Book 3 T, 1951-1979 (Box 84)
  - Great Britain-Royal Family-Queen Elizabeth II-Book 4 U -- Z and Miscellaneous, 1951-1974 (Box 84)
  - Green, Fred W. Ex-Governor-Book 1, 1926-1939 (Box 84)
  - Green, Fred W.-Ex-Governor-Book 2, 1920-1936 (Box 85)
  - Green, William-Labor Leader, 1929-1952 (Box 85)
  - Greenberg, Hank-Baseball, 1933-1982 (Box 85)
  - Gribbs, Roman S.-Detroit Mayor-Book 1-A-C, 1963-1979 (Box 85)
  - Gribbs, Roman S.-Detroit Mayor-Book 2-D-M, 1969-1974 (Box 85)
  - Gribbs, Roman S.-Detroit Mayor-Book 3-M-Z and Miscellaneous, 1965-1976 (Box 85)
  - Griffin, Robert-Politician-Book 1 A-H, 1959-1976 (Box 86)
  - Griffin, Robert-Politician-Book 2 H-P, 1965-1978 (Box 86)
  - Griffin, Robert-Politician-Book 3 P-S, 1960-1978 (Box 86)
  - Griffin, Robert-Politician-Book 4 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1956-1977 (Box 86)
  - Griffiths, Martha-Politician, 1946-1982 (Box 86)
  - Groesbeck, Alex-Michigan Governor-Book 1 A-F, 1920-1953 (Box 87)
  - Groesbeck, Alex-Michigan Governor-Book 2 G, 1920-1934 (Box 87)
  - Groesbeck, Alex-Michigan Governor-Book 3 H-Z and Miscellaneous, 1926-1956 (Box 87)
  - Gromyko, Andrei-Politician, 1943-1979 (Box 87)
  - Hannah, John-Michigan State University President, 1941-1971 (Box 87)
  - Hammarskjold, Dag-Diplomat, 1955-1972 (Box 88)
  - Harding, Warran G.-President-Book 1, 1920-1965 (Box 88)
  - Harding, Warran G.-President-Book 2, 1920-1923 (Box 88)
  - Hare, James M.-Politician, 1952-1967 (Box 88)
  - Harriman, W. Averell-Politician, 1941-1969 (Box 88)
  - Hart, Philip-Politician-Book 1 A-G, 1952-1975 (Box 88)
  - Hart, Philip-Politician Book 2 H-P 1941-1973 (Box 89)
  - Hart, Philip-Politician Book 3 R-Z-Miscellaneous 1957-1975 (Box 89)
  - Hauptmann, Bruno R.-Kidnapper-Book 1 (Box 89)
  - Hauptmann, Bruno R.-Kidnapper-Book 2 (Box 89)
  - Hearst, Patricia-Folder 1, 1974-1975 (Box 89)
  - Hearst, Patricia-Folder 2, 1974-1984 (Box 90)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1948-1980 (Box 90)
  - Hitler, Adolf-German Dictator-Book 1 A-C, 1934-1936 (Box 90)
  - Hitler, Adolf-German Dictator-Book 2 D-O, 1935-1981 (Box 90)
  - Hitler, Adolf-German Dictator-Book 3 P-S, 1930-1973 (Box 90)
  - Hitler, Adolf-German Dictator-Book 4 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1930-1982 (Box 91)
  - Hockey, 1962-1982 (Box 91)
  - Hoffa, James R.-Union Official-Book 1 A-D, 1957-1978 (Box 91)
  - Hoffa, James R.-Union Official-Book 2 D-M, 1958-1980 (Box 91)
  - Hoffa, James R.-Union Official-Book 3 N-T, 1957-1980 (Box 91)
  - Hoffa, James R.-Unions Official-Book 4 T, 1956-1973 (Box 92)
  - Hoffa, James R.-Unions Official-Book 5 T, 1957-1975 (Box 92)
  - Hoffa, James R.-Unions Official-Book 6 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1938-1982 (Box 92)
  - Homes-Idea, 1926-1982 (Box 92)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar-FBI Director, 1931-1977 (Box 92)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 1, 1919-1959 (Box 93)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 2, 1917-1953 (Box 93)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 3, 1919-1964 (Box 93)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 4, 1920-1964 (Box 93)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 5, 1928-1941 (Box 94)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 6, 1920-1945 (Box 94)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 7, 1926-1954 (Box 94)
  - Hoover, Herbert-Book 8, 1928-1973 (Box 94)
  - House of David, 1907-1977 (Box 95)
  - Houses-Repairs-Series, 1971-1977 (Box 95)
  - Housing-Group-Detroit-Herman Gardens-Graft, 1940-1945 (Box 95)
  - Howe, Gordie-Hockey-A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1957-1975 (Box 95)
  - Hubbard, Orville-Politician-Book 1 A-N, 1952-1976 (Box 95)
  - Hubbard, Orville-Politician-Book 2 O-Z and Miscellaneous, 1921-1982 (Box 96)
  - Hughes, Howard-Aviator and Movie Producer, 1942-1980 (Box 96)
  - Humphrey, George M.-Politician, 1952-1970 (Box 96)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H.-Politician-Book 1 A-E, 1952-1977 (Box 96)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H.-Politician-Book 2 F-P, 1949-1976 (Box 96)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H.-Politician-Book 3, 1959-1975 (Box 96)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H.-Politician-Book 4, 1952-1976 (Box 97)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H.-Politician-Book 5, 1957-1981 (Box 97)
  - Iran-Foreign Relations-U.S.-Book 1, 1936-1979 (Box 97)
  - Iran-Foreign Relations-U.S.-Book 2, 1979-1980 (Box 97)
  - Iran-Foreign Relations-U.S.-Book 3, 1980 (Box 97)
  - Iran-Foreign Relations-U. S.-Book 4, 1981-1982 (Box 98)
  - Iran-Royal Families-Shah Mohammed Reza Pahlavi-Book 1, 1948-1979 (Box 98)
  - Iran-Royal Families-Shah Mohammed Reza Pahlavi-Book 2, 1926-1971 (Box 98)
  - Jeffries, Edward J. Jr.-Book 1, 1931-1950 (Box 98)
  - Jeffries, Edward J. Jr.-Book 2, 1938-1959 (Box 98)
  - Jeffries Sr., Edward J.-Detroit, 1918-1960 (Box 98)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 1 A, 1963-1969 (Box 99)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 2 B, 1963-1975 (Box 99)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 3 C, 1953-1970 (Box 99)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 4 D-E, 1956-1973 (Box 99)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 5 E-F, 1963-1968 (Box 100)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 6 G-H, 1955-1973 (Box 100)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 7 H-K, 1960-1968 (Box 100)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 8 L-M, 1963-1972 (Box 100)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 9 M, 1956-1968 (Box 100)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 10 M-P, 1958-1968 (Box 101)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 11 P, 1960-1969 (Box 101)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 12 P-R, 1960-1969 (Box 101)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 13 R-S, 1956-1977 (Box 101)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 14 S-T, 1959-1968 (Box 102)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 15 T, 1961-1974 (Box 102)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 16 T, 1960-1968 (Box 102)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 17 V, 1967 (Box 102)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.-President-Book 18 V, 1980 (Box 102)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon B., 1963-1982 (Box 103)
  - Kefauver, Estes-Politician-Book 1 A-P, 1949-1965 (Box 103)
  - Kefauver, Estes-Politician-Book 2 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1939-1963 (Box 103)
  - Kefauver, Estes-Politician-Folder, 1958-1959 (Box 103)
  - Kelley, Frank J.-Politician-Book 1 A-E, 1963-1982 (Box 103)
  - Kelley, Frank J.-Politician-Book 2 F-P, 1964-1977 (Box 103)
  - Kelley, Frank J.-Politician-Book 3, P-S, 1962-1982 (Box 104)
  - Kelley, Frank J.-Politician-Book 4, S -- Z and Miscellaneous, 1962-1982 (Box 104)
  - Kelly, Harry F.-Michigan Politician-Book 1, 1931-1950 (Box 104)
  - Kelly, Harry F.-Michigan Politician-Book 2, 1939-1946 (Box 104)
  - Kennedy, Edward M.-Politician-Book 1 A-D, 1964-1978 (Box 104)
  - Kennedy, Edward M.-Politician-Book 2 E-P, 1958-1978 (Box 105)
  - Kennedy, Edward M.-Politician-Book 3 R-Z and Miscellaneous, 1960-1978 (Box 105)
  - Kennedy, Edward M.-Book 1, 1965-1981 (Box 105)
  - Kennedy, Edward M.-Book 2, 1962-1982 (Box 105)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 1 A, 1960-1975 (Box 105)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 2 A, 1962-1978 (Box 106)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 3 A-B, 1960-1979 (Box 106)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 4 B-C, 1961-1966 (Box 106)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 5 C, 1960-1975 (Box 106)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 6 D-E, 1956-1963 (Box 107)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 7 E, 1960-1972 (Box 107)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 8 G-I, 1961-1975 (Box 107)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 9 J-L, 1960-1971 (Box 107)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 10 M, 1961-1965 (Box 107)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 11 M, 1960-1963 (Box 108)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 12 N-P, 1960-1965 (Box 108)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 13 P, 1960-1974 (Box 108)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 14 P, 1959-1960 (Box 108)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 15 P, 1960-1968 (Box 108)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 16 S, 1956-1966 (Box 109)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 17 S-T, 1956-1981 (Box 109)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 18 T-U, 1960-1966 (Box 109)
  - Kennedy, John F.-President-Book 19 W-Z and Miscellaneous, 1959-1982 (Box 109)
  - Kennedy, Robert F.-Politician-Book 1 A-H, 1962-1982 (Box 109)
  - Kennedy, Robert F.-Politician-Book 2 I-N, 1957-1974 (Box 110)
  - Kennedy, Robert F.-Politician-Book 3 N-S, 1961-1968 (Box 110)
  - Kennedy, Robert F.-Politician-Book 4 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1957-1978 (Box 110)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita-Russian Official-Book 1 A-D, 1955-1971 (Box 110)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita-Russian Official-Book 2 E-K, 1953-1973 (Box 110)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita-Russian Official-Book 3 L-R, 1958-1978 (Box 111)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita-Russian Official-Book 4 S-T, 1955-1964 (Box 111)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita-Russian Official-Book 5 T, 1955-1979 (Box 111)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita-Russian Official-Book 6 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1955-1982 (Box 111)
  - King Jr., Martin Luther-Civil Rights Leader-Book 1 A-Z, 1957-1982 (Box 111)
  - King Jr., Martin Luther-Civil Rights Leader-Book 2 Miscellaneous, 1956-1981 (Box 112)
  - Kissinger, Henry A.-Secretary of State-Book 1 A-E, 1961-1981 (Box 112)
  - Kissinger, Henry A.-Secretary of State-Book 2 F-M, 1962-1980 (Box 112)
  - Kissinger, Henry A.-Secretary of State-Book 3 N-S, 1957-1982 (Box 112)
  - Kissinger, Henry A.-Secretary of State-Book 4 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1969-1982 (Box 112)
  - Kosygin, Alexei-Russian Premier-A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1948-1980 (Box 113)
  - Labor-Unions-Inquiry-Book 1, 1937-1958 (Box 113)
  - Labor-Unions-Inquiry-Book 2, 1957-1963 (Box 113)
  - Labor-Unions-Teamsters-Inquiry-Book 1, 1953-1959 (Box 113)
  - Labor-Unions-Teamsters-Inquiry-Book 2, 1957-1964 (Box 113)
  - Laird, Melvin R-Politician-A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1969-1973 (Box 114)
  - Landon, Alfred M.-Kansas Politician, 1935-1977 (Box 114)
  - Leonard, Donald S.-Police Commissioner, 1931-1977 (Box 114)
  - Lewis, John L.-Labor Leader-Book 1 A-S, 1933-1969 (Box 114)
  - Lewis, John L.-Labor Leader-Book 2 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1924-1982 (Box 114)
  - Lincoln, Abraham-President-Book 1 A-L, 1918-1969 (Box 115)
  - Lincoln, Abraham-President-Book 2 M-Z and Miscellaneous, 1922-1983 (Box 115)
  - Lindbergh, Charles-Aviator-Book 1 A-F, 1927-1977 (Box 115)
  - Lindbergh, Charles-Aviator-Book 2 F-O, 1927-1978 (Box 115)
  - Lindbergh, Charles-Aviator-Book 3, 1927-1978 (Box 115)
  - Lindbergh, Charles Jr.-Kidnapped, 1932-1982 (Box 116)
  - Lindsey, John V.-Politician, 1964-1978 (Box 116)
  - Liston, Sonny-Boxer, 1959-1965 (Box 116)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot Jr.-Politician, 1940-1976 (Box 116)
  - Lodge, John C.-Book 1 A-L, 1918-1935 (Box 116)
  - Lodge, John C.-Book 2 M-Z and Miscellaneous, 1927-1973 (Box 116)
  - Louis, Joe-Boxer-Book 1, 1934-1981 (Box 117)
  - Louis, Joe-Boxer-Book 2, 1935-1981 (Box 117)
  - MacArthur, Douglas-Army Officer-Book 1, 1917-1981 (Box 117)
  - MacArthur, Douglas-Army Officer-Book 2, 1927-1972 (Box 117)
  - MacArthur, Douglas-Army Officer-Book 3, 1942-1982 (Box 117)
  - MacMillan, Harold-British Statesman-Book 1 A-J, 1942-1974 (Box 118)
  - MacMillan, Harold-British Statesman & Wife-Book 2 K-Z and Miscellaneous, 1955-1980 (Box 118)
  - Mao Tse-Tung-Communist Party Leader-A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1945-1981 (Box 118)
  - Marshall, General George Catlett-Statesman-Book 1 A-P, 1940-1972 (Box 118)
  - Marshall, General George Catlett-Statesman-Book 2 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1939-1973 (Box 118)
  - McCarthy, Eugene J.-Politician, 1928-1954 (Box 118)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R.-Senator-Book 1 A-C, 1950-1973 (Box 119)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R.-Senator-Book 2 C-G, 1950-1978 (Box 119)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R.-Senator-Book 3 G-Z and Miscellaneous, 1946-1982 (Box 119)
  - McCrea, Duncan C.-Prosecutor-Book 1 A-N, 1932-1951 (Box 119)
  - McCrea, Duncan C.-Prosecutor-Book 2 O-Z and Miscellaneous, 1926-1950 (Box 119)
  - McDivitt, James A.-Astronaut, 1961-1977 (Box 119)
  - McGovern, George S.-Politician-Book 1 A-P, 1962-1980 (Box 120)
  - McGovern, George S.-Politician-Book 2 P, 1968-1972 (Box 120)
  - McGovern, George S.-Politician-Book 3 P, 1967-1975 (Box 120)
  - McGovern, George S.-Politician-Book 4 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1967-1982 (Box 120)
  - McKay, Frank D.-Book 1, 1927-1966 (Box 120)
  - McKay, Frank D.-Book 2, 1940-1960 (Box 121)
  - McLain, Denny-Baseball, 1963-1982 (Box 121)
  - McNamara, Patrick V.-Politician, 1947-1977 (Box 121)
  - McNamara, Robert S.-Defense Secretary-Book 1 A-L, 1961-1971 (Box 121)
  - McNamara, Robert S.-Defense Secretary-Book 2 M-R, 1961-1967 (Box 121)
  - McNamara, Robert S.-Defense Secretary-Book 3 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1960-1982 (Box 121)
  - Meany, George-Labor Leader-Book 1 A-R, 1952-1980 (Box 122)
  - Meany, George-Labor Leader-Book 2 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1953-1980 (Box 122)
  - Michigan-Cities-Ecorse-Grand Jury, 1954-1959 (Box 122)
  - Michigan-Counties-Macomb-Grand Jury, 1956-1958 (Box 122)
  - Michigan-Counties-Macomb-Prosecutors-Inquiry, 1946-1956 (Box 122)
  - Michigan-Counties-Wayne-Elections-Results, 1927-1982 (Box 122)
  - Michigan-Counties-Wayne-Government-Inquiry, 1941-1945 (Box 123)
  - Michigan-Elections-Candidates, 1918-1982 (Box 123)
  - Michigan-Elections-Results-Book 1, 1917-1972 (Box 123)
  - Michigan-Elections-Results-Book 2, 1928-1954 (Box 123)
  - Michigan-Elections-Results-Book 3, 1954-1963 (Box 123)
  - Michigan-Elections-Results-Book 4, 1964-1982 (Box 123)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 1 A-B, 1957-1980 (Box 124)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 2 B, 1943-1948 (Box 124)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 3 B, 1945-1971 (Box 124)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 4 C, 1956-1982 (Box 124)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 5 C-E, 1953-1982 (Box 124)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 6 E-L, 1921-1982 (Box 125)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 7 M, 1937-1980 (Box 125)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 8 M, 1920-1981 (Box 125)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 9 M, 1922-1980 (Box 125)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 10 M-O, 1959-1982 (Box 126)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 11 P-R, 1923-1982 (Box 126)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 12 R, 1921-1953 (Box 126)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 13 R, 1953-1968 (Box 126)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 14 R-S, 1958-1982 (Box 127)
  - Michigan-Legislature-Book 15 S-Miscellaneous, 1962-1982 (Box 127)
  - Michigan Bell Telephone Company-Rates, 1913-1982 (Box 127)
  - Michigan Consolidated Gas Company, 1935-1941 (Box 127)
  - Michigan Consolidated Gas Company-Natural Gas, 1930-1977 (Box 127)
  - Michigan Consolidated Gas Company-Rates, 1923-1982 (Box 128)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 1 A, 1964-1982 (Box 128)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 2 B, 1967-1982 (Box 128)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 3 B-C, 1969-1982 (Box 128)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 4 D-F, 1966-1982 (Box 129)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 5 F, 1968-1982 (Box 129)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 6 G-F, 1964-1982 (Box 129)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 7 L-O, 1965-1982 (Box 129)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 8 P, 1962-1982 (Box 129)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 9 R-T, 1961-1982 (Box 130)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 10 T-U, 1971-1982 (Box 130)
  - Milliken, William G.-Governor-Book 11 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1965-1982 (Box 130)
  - Miriani, Louis C.-Detroit Mayor-Book 1 A-F, 1930-1966 (Box 130)
  - Miriani, Louis C.-Detroit Mayor-Book 2 G-Q, 1953-1969 (Box 130)
  - Miriani, Louis C.-Detroit Mayor-Book 3 R-Z and Miscellaneous, 1949-1969 (Box 131)
  - Moody, Blair-Senator, 1942-1960 (Box 131)
  - Motorboat-Races-Book 1 A -- L, 1927-1981 (Box 131)
  - Motorboat-Races-Book 3 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1920-1981 (Box 131)
  - Motorboat-Races-Gold Cup, 1920-1982 (Box 131)
  - Motorboat-Races-Harmsworth, 1921-1982 (Box 132)
  - Murders-Michigan-Ann Arbor Area, 1967-1982 (Box 132)
  - Murphy, Frank-Judge-Book 1 A-F, 1930-1949 (Box 132)
  - Murphy, Frank-Judge-Book 2 F-M, 1924-1972 (Box 132)
  - Murphy, Frank-Judge-Book 4 M-S, 1930-1959 (Box 132)
  - Murphy, Frank-Judge-Book 5 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1930-1967 (Box 132)
  - Nicklaus, Jack-Golfer, 1959-1982 (Box 133)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 1 A, 1955-1978 (Box 133)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 2 A, 1955-1979 (Box 133)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 3 A-B, 1954-1977 (Box 133)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 4 B, 1972 (Box 133)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 5 B-C, 1956-1980 (Box 134)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 6 C, 1954-1978 (Box 134)